This is Kobe!
It's so nice!
Oh man, my first time
in Kansai! I'm pumped!
All right. Next stop, my house, 'kay?
What's with those faces?
Obviously, we're gonna see the sights!
What, seriously? Isn't it hot?
What do you think, Yoi-chan?!
I'll go along with
whatever you guys decide.
All right! Sightseeing it is, then!
Yay!
Hyogo
Nankinmachi
That looks so good!
There's a panda one, too! So cute!
Wanna get it?
I'll pass. I'll wait here.
I'm not hungry either, so I'll wait, too.
Okay, then we'll be back in a bit.
I wonder what's in the panda one?
They're sure full of energy.
Man, it sure is hot.
Are you all right?
I naturally run hot,
so I can't stand this weather.
Oh...
If you'd like, you can
join me under the parasol?
Does that keep you cool?
Yes, it's cool.
Huh.
Oh, you're right.
It's a bit cooler.
Th-This doesn't make it cooler!
Is he doing this on purpose?
I'm amazed that you even
brought your parasol with you.
When I stand in the sun too long,
my skin turns bright red.
You do have fair skin, Yoi-chan.
Are you sure you're okay
staying behind, Senpai?
We came all the way to Chinatown...
Yeah.
I don't care what we do,
as long as I get to be with you.
And, well...
I want to flirt with you more.
Hey!
We went and bought it!
Huh? What's up?
Nothing.
Hey! That's mine!
I feel like...
Senpai is a little different
from his usual self today.
The clothes I bought and
the earrings, too...
Maybe I should have worn them.
Maybe...
The two of us should have
just come on our own.
Huh?
Anyway, just have a seat wherever.
W-Wow! This is insane!
Oh, man, amazing! Thanks for having me.
Is your boyfriend's family an oil tycoon?
Your house is amazing, but
this is really something, too.
I-I don't think so.
Is anyone hungry?
I'm about to order.
What do you guys want?
I'm hungry!
Since we have the chance,
I'd like to watch something
while we eat pizza and stuff!
A slingshot isn't going to cut it!
Millie, please wake up!
What's gonna happen?!
Oh, you want me to spoil it?
Don't you dare!
Everyone, run away!
Does anyone want something to drink?
Oh, I'm good.
Me, too.
Me, too. Thanks.
Yoi-chan?
Oh, I could get it my—
It's all right, I'll get it for you.
Tea okay?
Yes, sorry to trouble you.
Senpai...
He sort of mentioned how he keeps
the location of his house a secret.
Was it really okay for me to ask him
to bring my friends here too?
Hey, are we really gonna end up
watching this til season two?
Wouldn't it be faster if I just
spoiled it for you all?
Like I said, don't you dare!
Hey! They're flirting!
You're so loud.
That's shameless, shameless I say!
I'm just sitting next to her.
I think I'm doing great
at containing myself.
Anyway, look, Millie's in trouble.
What?
Ah! Why is Millie the
only one with powers?!
Well, yeah...
It's true...
He is just sitting next to me, but...
Hey.
Huh?! Oh, yes?
I...
want to hang out tonight.
Just the two of us.
Okay.
I said, "Okay," without giving
it much thought, but...
It'll be all right... Right?
And, well...
I want to flirt with you more.
N-No, that can't be it!
Besides...
I don't care what we do,
as long as I get to be with you.
Just... how do I put it...
You have a new message.
Today
Are you still awake?
Y-Yes... I'm still awake.
Hmm.
Excuse me.
Senpai... just got out of the bath.
How about the others?
Oh, they're already asleep.
How about your friends, Senpai?
Kuwa's already asleep, but Sentaro
is playing games in the room.
I told him I was going to
shower and forced my way out.
Um, Senpai, did you have fun today?
Huh? Why d'you ask?
Well, you let my friends
come along because I asked.
But maybe our first summer break together
should have been just us, like you said.
You taking this too seriously?
Huh?
You don't have to worry
about things like that.
We won't get many chances like this,
and it's been pretty fun.
It's kinda like a school trip, y'know?
Oh... I get it.
We won't be going on our school trip
or graduating in the same year...
I see.
But, well, to be honest,
if it was just the two of us,
we could've flirted a bit more.
I'm telling you right now,
there will be none of that today.
Even holding hands?
Not even a hug? Are you serious?!
Yes.
You're... serious...
I mean, don't you think you're a little
excessive with physical contact, Senpai?
In various ways...
That's because.
If you like someone, isn't it
normal to want to touch them?
Am I wrong?
Oh, gosh!
I-I won't deny that, but...
are you always like this
when you date a girl?
Huh?
Must have been my imagination.
Oh!
There's pizza left over.
Why do we have to hide?!
'Cause it'll be a pain
if he goes off again.
But it doesn't mean he had to
go right from that to this...
I don't know any other way.
Up until now... I thought dating just
meant sticking together and making out.
I thought that's what it
meant to be in love.
But...
When it comes to you, Yoi-chan,
as much as I want you and
want to get to know you more...
at the same time...
I also want to cherish you.
I have these conflicting feelings.
Still...
I don't know any other way to express
my feelings other than by "touching,"
so sometimes I don't know what to do.
I sorta...
don't even know what I'm saying anymore.
Wh-Who even is this awkward person?
I don't care what we do,
as long as I get to be with you.
It's the same feeling as
when I heard those words...
This feeling that bubbles
up inside my heart...
Just what do you call this feeling?
Mi amore!
Um...
If you'd like...
Before we leave tomorrow,
we could go someplace together.
L-Like... on a date.
Sure.
Let's do it.
W-Well then, I guess we
should head to bed.
Hmm.
For tomorrow... Is ten too early?
No.
Then let's meet in the living room at ten.
Hmm.
G-Good night.
What's up?
A hug.
May I please...
have a goodnight hug?
Hey...
You messing with me?
Besides, you're the one
who said it, didn't you?
Sayin' there'd be none of that.
I-I know.
But I feel like I kinda understand
what you were saying.
I want to cherish you...
but I want to touch you.
That's why, right now,
I want to touch you, Senpai.
You're killin' me.
I know.
Good night.
Oh, man, what is this?
What am I... What am I even doing?!
I can't stay calm...
Just thinking about it is embarrassing...
But still...
Senpai's body temperature...
The feel of his arms...
The smell of his shampoo, his breathing...
All of it, all of it, all of it,
is ruminating in my brain.
I'm losing myself.
Oh, did you just get out of the bath?
Gotta say, that was awfully long.
Who are you, Shizuka-chan?
Nah.
Come again?
Just what do you...
call this feeling?
Wh-Wha, what? What? What's wrong?!
My glasses, glasses...
Um...
Actually, I have something I need
to talk to you guys about.
Um!
I'm sorry for being late.
It took a bit longer
than I thought, and...
Hey, Yoi-chan, you seem a
bit sparkly today, yeah?
Wh-What do you mean by that?!
No, how should I put it...
Nah, actually never mind.
Don't worry about it.
Anyway, let's go before it gets hot.
I actually had Nobara and Kotobuki
do a few things for me, but...
I wanted a little more of
a reaction... I guess.
Did Ichi leave already?
Probably.
Damn it, they're coming!
Let's go!
I don't want them to see
how you look today.
I suppose...
that I'll take that as a compliment.
You can.
It's almost like he's shining.
It's making me dizzy.
Wow!
What a beautiful aquarium.
I did a little research last night.
Oh, hey.
What is it?
I would like to hold your hand.
Um!
Yes!
One vote... in favor.
Koi Food
Here.
It's good, so...
Oh, this is cute.
A gift for your friends?
Oh, it's for my big sis.
What, you have a big sis?
Big Sister
Oh, yes.
Do you want to see a pic?
Huh, you guys don't look much alike.
I get that a lot.
Unlike me...
My big sister looks very girly,
so she's always been popular.
Uh-huh...
During my first year of junior high,
there was a boy I had a
little crush on and...
Hey, I wonder if Takiguchi
has a crush on you.
What are ya gonna do if
she confesses to you?
Huh?!
There's no way I can date a
girl who's taller than me.
Would've been better if it was
her big sis instead.
What?!
Where does he live?
What's his high school?
Middle school?
P-Please stop.
Elementary?
What ward, what block,
what building, what number?
It's all in the past.
Oh, I'm gonna find out.
Still...
I think that's when I sort of started
to have trouble talking to guys...
Oh, but I do love my big sis, so I'm
honestly happy when she gets praised.
I see now.
So, that's the cause of
your low self-esteem.
Can you show me your sis one more time?
Oh, sure.
Yeah, I like you better.
Wh-What about me?
Hmm? Well, your face?
I shouldn't have asked.
Do you have any siblings, Senpai?
I do. One older brother.
Oh.
He's a fine young man.
A steady, honest, upstanding citizen.
What? I kind of... can't picture that.
He is the total opposite of me.
Dunno where he is or what
he's doing right now.
Does that mean...
Some things happened
between him and his ex.
He fought with our parents, too.
Haven't heard from him since.
Well...
Life's full of surprises, yeah?
He made it sound like nothing, but
that's not a common situation at all.
Why was he talking about his own family
like it was someone else's problem?
Yoi-chan!
See ya.
You should've said something.
What is it? What's wrong?
Those people you were with just now...
Oh, I just picked up a
cellphone they dropped.
Uh-huh...
Huh, could it be that...
you're jealous?
I-It's nothing like that!
I'm heading out.
Huh? Yoi-san, I was just kiddin'!
Oh... Why am I always like this?
Whoa, amazing.
Right?
Yes.
What? Still sulking?
I-I am certainly—
not... sulking.
Really. It's just...
I'm disgusted with myself.
Because...
We were just having a serious
conversation about your family,
but then seeing you with other girls
quickly made me lose my confidence,
and on top of that, I became
completely preoccupied with myself,
Huh, wordy much?
and as if that wasn't enough, I ended
up making you have to cheer me up...
I should have just admitted I was jealous.
But instead, I ended up thinking
those girls would suit you better
than someone who's putting in all her
effort just to wear a dress for once.
He was right.
I really do have low self-esteem, don't I?
Yoi-chan...
Y'know how you don't look
at me as the Prince?
You've treated me as one of
the guys right from the get-go.
Well, maybe you just
didn't like me at first...
But... I feel like I can be myself
when I'm with you, Yoi-chan.
Laughing at stupid things.
Holding hands while we walk.
Eating gyoza, eating dango, and
talking side-by-side at night.
Seriously, just being with you is so fun.
When I saw my bro broken,
I honestly thought
"He's so lame for feeling broken
over something silly like love."
But now, I'm thinking that
love is pretty cool.
Talk about your teenage cliché, right?
I never thought I'd ever dress like this
for someone and go on a date, either.
Um...
I chose these earrings,
because I thought they looked similar
to yours and we could match.
I thought that might be the case.
We should head back soon.
I...
I think I'm going to end up
loving him more and more.
You could have...
kissed me, y'know.
A Goodnight Hug
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Yukari Murase-Louden
Andy Ellis
Gabriella Alabanza
Salem Alabanza
Elizabeth Ellis